{"posts":[{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"can we submit the report as a number of files that contain each part needed i.e the log book the er model class diagram being in separate files under the 'report' folder or does it have to be in one file in the folder","answers":[{"text":"please merge it into one report pdf if possible.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"how should we submit the final report is there any give command or just push it to github thanks","answers":[{"text":"report folder within master branch. there is no give command only github.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi could you tell me what type of classes from our class diagram do we not include in the er diagram for example we're assuming we don't include classes such as providermanager in the er diagram.","answers":[{"text":"also we're on the same team do inherited entities not need a primary key thanks.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi for the class diagram do we need to include classes that inherit from exception also i'm not too sure what methods that create decorators return e.g. patient_required since i used the lab08 code for login in terms of that.","answers":[{"text":"i'm not a tutor but i dont think exceptions should be in the class diagram as they arent part of the system","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"exceptions are not really part of the business domain. i personally would not model them.","theta":1,"count":0}]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi i am wondering whether all team members need to give the presentation i know all the members should attend to the lab but should all team members give the presentation together","answers":[{"text":"hi zhilin i would highly recommend all team members to actively participate in the project demonstration as this also plays a part in the quality of your presentation.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"thanks for your reply","theta":1,"count":0}]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"pytest all our test cases are done except for flexible partial name searches etc. our search function returns a list of providers how do we use asserts to test what this returns should i make a separate function for this an example of part of our code thanks","answers":[{"text":"hey sai one way you could test your search function is to compare its output with the expected output. since your function returns a list of providers please take a look at list/set comparison methods. i am guessing you have multiple search functions so i agree with you on making a separate function for the comparison.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"just wondering if we need to create test cases for this because according to this we only need to create tests cases for the 3 core user stories https //webcms3.cse.unsw.edu.au/static/uploads/cou...","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"yes test-cases are only needed for the the above user-stories","theta":1,"count":0}]]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"question about test cases just wanna confirm that we only need to create test cases for these 3 user stories https //webcms3.cse.unsw.edu.au/static/uploads/cou...","answers":[{"text":"yup that's right.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi can someone please clarify how to use give to submit","answers":[{"text":"there is no give submission push to final release branch as shown in specs. the name of branch is case sensitive so copy it exactly from specs.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"thanks for reply but for final report all uml diagram do we still need to push to final_release branch or some other way to submit","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"please put report inside final_release branch within a folder named 'report'.","theta":1,"count":0}]]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"attributeerror 'str' object has no attribute 'login' i'm doing the pytest and occur this error. how can i fix that","answers":[{"text":"hey haonan the error just indicates that self._auth_manager is of type string and not the type it is meant to be. please have a look at where you assigned the value to self._auth_manager.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"doing the final checks of the specification and the code i've come up with a query - pytest for our system we handle the majority of the error checking on the front end and presume all data is sanitised and corrected by the front end so our backend has very little data checking outside of a few functions where appropriate currently we have a full coverage testing of searching and making appointments along with a few minor other functions such as whether or not you can book with x provider and new_referral. - we don't have any tests for managing patient history notes / viewing patient history since all of that is handled by the front end for example on an appointment we store the provider that was part of that appointment along with the patient so we can simply just check if you were the provider that made such appointment and if so then you can edit the notes . i've read previously that in this case we wouldn't have to test the history and just want to confirm this d.","answers":[{"text":"pytests will not be required for front-end validation checks e g. if a required input has not been provided date-formats etc.. however use-cases such as editing patient history would still require to be checked using pytests as these are not mere front-end validation checks and adding notes to an existing patient's history does invoke a back-end function and results in a change to the model in this case the patient's history data.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi i was wondering whether we should remove acceptance criteria related to visuals out of our user stories for example there is a calendar widget because it's hard to implement pytest for these cases. thanks","answers":[{"text":"angela you do not need to remove the acceptance criteria related to front-end validation or view components. these can be verified by customer during end-of-iteration demo i.e uat by customer in this case the tutor . pytests are only required for back-end functionality","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi since previous spec states every provider has a profession what is the profession of specialist","answers":[{"text":"hi william the profession of a specialist is left for you to decide based on what best helps the user the profession could simply be 'specialist' or the field of expertise associated with the specialist. you should be able to support your decision with a clear reason.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"in the spec it says each healthcare provider seen by the patient may request access to able to view/edit the history of the patient to add their specific notes during the consultation with the patient. healthcare providers will not be able to edit the past history recorded by other providers but will only be able to add their own specific notes about the patient s visit. but then in the scenarios it seems as if those who a patient books with automatically get access to the notes who is receiving/approving this request am i missing something here are my two interpretations 1. once the patient books with a provider they automatically can click on the patients history add new notes but cannot change old notes. in this case the request is either a poor choice of words or a request to the server 2. once the patient books with a provider the provider can request to the patient or provider to be able to view previous notes then the patient or provider can click accept of some sort to enable access. another question this example has also confused me healthcare providers in healthcare centres that the patient has not visited must not have access to the patient s history. does this imply that if a user goes to a health provider at health centre x every other provider at health centre x does have a copy of the patients history","answers":[{"text":"hi owen for the first question both will be considered acceptable but i would recommend the first option. as for the second question only the health providers that has/had an appointment with a particular patient may access their appointments history.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi is adding more than one note per appointment required from the spec also is it okay to have a user's userid consist of their password and username combined thanks.","answers":[{"text":"hi angela adding multiple notes per appointment is not required for this project. as for the second part i can see why you might want to use username password as a user-id but using an attribute or set of attributes that is subject to changes is usually not recommended for use as a primary key. additionally having a key that consists of more than 1 attributes is not recommended for complexity amp efficiency issues. in the case like this i advise introducing a separate 'id' attribute whose value is uniquely assigned for each user e.g. increment by 1 for every new user . cheers","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"committing in the last 48 hours. i was under the impression that as long as you don't commit everything is the last 48 hours you will not lose marks but apparently if you commit even something small it will result to lost marks. so is this assignment due monday 10am or saturday 10am","answers":[{"text":"where majority of work is done in last 48 hours. that will be fixed sorry.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"the specification states that the software should also be submitted by give command. what is the command for milestone3 submission cheers","answers":[{"text":"hi di wu we have decided that there is no need for give submissions for the milestone 3. there will be an update announcement soon.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"according to the specs a registered user should be able to update their profile details. do these updates need to reflect across even after the web server is stopped and rerun or should these updated details only persist as long as the web server is kept running","answers":[{"text":"persistence of data is required for this final iteration. you can do so by saving objects to files using pickle then loading them back up on server start.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"there is a 500 server error when trying to access the sample project link is http //cgi.cse.unsw.edu.au/ cs1531/18s2/sample_project/run.cgi/ . can this be fixed or is it being purposefully shut down","answers":[{"text":"would like to know this too.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi i have a question about who can see a patients history. the spec has these two points a provider is granted access to a patient s history only after the patient has made an appointment with the provider. healthcare providers in healthcare centres that the patient has not visited must not have access to the patient s history. does this means that if a patient jack has an appointment with provider ian at centre a provider toby who also works at centre a should not be able to see jacks history if so then isn't the second point redundant since all that matters is that the patient has an appointment with the provider not the centre the provider works at. however if toby can see jacks history the first point is violated since toby doesn't have an appointment with jack. can someone please clarify whether or not toby can see jacks history thanks","answers":[{"text":"providers who have appointments with toby should be the only people who ever have access to the patient toby history. look at the examples.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi i was just wondering whether a provider can only add notes for patients during the consultation and after the consultation the provider cannot edit the patients' notes right like provider feels unhappy for the notes her took during the consultation and she wants to edit it after the consultation.","answers":[{"text":"each healthcare provider seen by the patient may request access to able to view/edit the history of the patient to add their specific notes during the consultation with the patient. healthcare providers will not be able to edit the past history recorded by other providers but will only be able to add their own specific notes about the patient s visit. from specs i'd interpret this as able to edit your own past notes not other providers.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"also can the provider anna view the profiles of her past patients who do not have appointments with anna currently","theta":1,"count":0}]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi can only providers who are a gp refer a patient to a specialist or can any provider refer a patient to a specialist thanks","answers":[{"text":"general practioners sending referrals to specialists where gp's and specialists are grouped under providers. interpret that how you will.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi i was just wondering if we need to register new users for the 3rd milestone.the spec was vague about this so i'm not sure what to do.","answers":[{"text":"you do not need to register new users as this would require you to implement additional functionality. you are only required to use the set of credentials provided in the csv files","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi looking through the specialist and provider csv files i noticed that gary gmail.com is present in both lists. considering patients can only book appointments with specialists after being referred to by a provider do we treat gary as a provider or a specialist","answers":[{"text":"sorry that must be a mistake. to keep it simple you can continue to treat gary as a provider and not as a specialist.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi right now our group reads from csv files to instantiate providers patients etc. in order to change this to be stored on pickle and use dao classes is dumping the patients providers etc. into a pickle file after reading and then loading enough or should reading from the csv files to instantiate not even happen","answers":[{"text":"the csv files have been provided so that you will not need to build any register user functionality. you simply use the set of users provided to you in the csv files. so one way would be to just read the csv file as a one-off and then use pickle to save and reload the data. you don't need to read the csv each time the app starts as long as the file dumped by pickle exists.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"for the patient history if a provider has access to a certain patients history as they have been visited in the past do they have access to the patient's entire history or only the appointments that were with that particular provider","answers":[{"text":"the provider will have access to the patient's entire history. the objective of the centralised history is provide access to the patient's complete history to all providers that the patient has visited","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"for some of the errors my group has handled them through the implementation of the front end but according to the deliverable document pytests are required to be written for them - does this mean i can ignore those test cases or should i change the way the errors are handled","answers":[{"text":"it is absolutely fine and in fact this is often the case if some validation errors are handled by the front-end. pytests are more about testing the working of back-end software to ensure that it behaves as expected for e.g. you could be testing a search for cases such as case insensitivity partial string match etc.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi with regards to the milestone 3 spec just wanted some clarification for history viewing privileges. here are some scenarios patient jack has an upcoming appointment with provider tony at centre a. provider anna also works at centre a however jack has never seen anna. will anna be able to access jack's history once the appointment is complete does tony still have access to jack's history if so will tony be able to see appointments made and completed after his own with other providers possibly at different centres thank you","answers":[{"text":"laura if provider anna has never seen patient jack then anna will not have access to jack's history. only the providers that tony has seen could be at different centres will be able to access jack's history. of course patient jack always has access to his own complete history.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"assignments","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"group project milestone 3","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"milestone 3 specification changes","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi i was wondering whether use of sqlalchemy is required for this iteration or is using pickle fine thanks","answers":[{"text":"we have not specified for a specific type of persistence so using pickle is fine.","theta":1,"count":0}]}]}